{
    "subject": "resource/Fire_Blade_(video_game)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Game",
    "human_readable": "Fire Blade is a type of Game.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9167731404304504,
            "question": "Is Fire Blade a type of entertainment?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7539495825767517,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a game similar to Fire Blade?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.662503719329834,
            "question": "What are some popular elements found in games like Fire Blade?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6480674147605896,
            "question": "Who might enjoy playing a game like Fire Blade?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5756222605705261,
            "question": "What makes Fire Blade unique compared to other games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5720962882041931,
            "question": "What category does Fire Blade belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5371031761169434,
            "question": "Are there any specific skills needed to play Fire Blade?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4577350914478302,
            "question": "What platforms is Fire Blade available on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4231567084789276,
            "question": "Are there any popular franchises similar to Fire Blade?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2748173475265503,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges players might face in Fire Blade?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fire Blade is a type of Game.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6302_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any popular franchises similar to Fire Blade?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6302_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What platforms is Fire Blade available on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6302_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any specific skills needed to play Fire Blade?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6302_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6302_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6302_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6302_149.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6302_155.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6302_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6302_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6302_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6302_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6302_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6302_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information clearly describes \"Fire Blade\" as a game, specifically a helicopter combat game for the PlayStation 2. Therefore, the statement that \"Fire Blade is a type of Game\" is supported by the provided documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}